<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-12T13:00:36-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">QA Ramblings</title><subtitle>My attempt to play with a github.io site, and list all the new things I am learning about being in QA</subtitle><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><entry><title type="html">Definition of Ready</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-of-Ready/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Definition of Ready" /><published>2018-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-of-Ready</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-of-Ready/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;After some discussion on DoD, we want to talk a little about what it means for a story to be Ready&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we were talking about the Definition of Done, it got some conversations going to talk about the Definition of Ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does your team have a definition of ready for your stories?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you include in your definition?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acceptance Criteria?Test Cases?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has your team looked into creating a Definition of Ready?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you use this DoR as a guideline to know when a story is ready to be worked on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A “ready” backlog item needs to be clear, feasible and testable:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts on a DoR?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="[&quot;Questions&quot;]" /><category term="Quality Questions" /><category term="Definition of Ready" /><summary type="html">After some discussion on DoD, we want to talk a little about what it means for a story to be Ready</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Test Cases</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/questions/Test-Cases/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test Cases" /><published>2018-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/questions/Test-Cases</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/questions/Test-Cases/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;One outcome from Acceptance Criteria is easily creatable test cases&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One possible outcome of spending time gathering Acceptance Criteria for stories is that you have now collected information that can be easily used as test cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How else do you go about gathering test cases?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things to think about when writing test cases:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test Cases need to be simple and transparent&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test Cases can &amp;amp; should be written by everyone(different people provide different perspective)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tests should be able to be rerun and always produce the same results&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you write test cases, do you only test for the good cases?  Do you test for edge cases?  Do you test for errors? Do you check the status of a web service call or do you always assume you will get a 200 response?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="[&quot;Questions&quot;]" /><category term="Quality Questions" /><category term="Test Cases" /><summary type="html">One outcome from Acceptance Criteria is easily creatable test cases</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Acceptance Criteria</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/questions/Acceptance-Criteria/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Acceptance Criteria" /><published>2018-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/questions/Acceptance-Criteria</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/questions/Acceptance-Criteria/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;After some discussion on DoD, we are going to this week talk about an element of most DoDs - Acceptance Criteria&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week I asked questions about Definition of Done, one item that should probably be part of every DoD is Acceptance Criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week I left a lot of question with no answers, this week, I’m going to provide a few thoughts along with my questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When do you write your acceptance criteria? Backlo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the point of acceptance criteria?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;define boundaries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;get consensus and understanding of story&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;serve as a basis for tests&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;help with planning and estimations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;get definition of expectations of product owner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What must Acceptance criteria include?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It needs to define when something is complete and working as expected, the criteria should be written clearly, in simple language the customer would use, without ambiguity regarding the expected outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What format do you use, when you write your  Acceptance criteria?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="[&quot;Questions&quot;]" /><category term="Quality Questions" /><category term="Acceptance Criteria" /><summary type="html">After some discussion on DoD, we are going to this week talk about an element of most DoDs - Acceptance Criteria</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Definition of Done</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-Of-Done/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Definition of Done" /><published>2018-09-10T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-Of-Done</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/questions/Definition-Of-Done/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This is the first in what I hope will be a series of posts I am writing, that I will also be sending to the development team at Miami&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When do I consider things done?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Does everyone on my team know what it means for something to be considered done? Do we have a Team Definition of Done?  Do we always follow the DoD?  Do I speak up if I don’t think everything is really done? Do we see value in our DoD?  Are there additional things that we can do to improve the quality of what we deliver?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How can your team improve your definition of done?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Can Solution Delivery do things to improve our collective definition of done for everything we deliver?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are the different things we can create a DoD for?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;TD Tickets? Jira Tasks? Stories in Jira? Projects? Are their others I haven’t listed?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add comments below sharing thoughts on DoD and what you use it for &amp;amp; how it is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="[&quot;Questions&quot;]" /><category term="Quality Questions" /><category term="Definition of Done" /><category term="DoD" /><summary type="html">This is the first in what I hope will be a series of posts I am writing, that I will also be sending to the development team at Miami</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Counterstrings created in Alfred Workflow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tools/counterstring-alfred-workflow-created/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Counterstrings created in Alfred Workflow" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tools/counterstring-alfred-workflow-created</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tools/counterstring-alfred-workflow-created/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;After learning about a counterstring while talking to someone at CAST, I had to make it easier for me to use them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="[&quot;Tools&quot;]" /><category term="Alfred Workflow" /><category term="CounterString" /><category term="QA Tools" /><summary type="html">After learning about a counterstring while talking to someone at CAST, I had to make it easier for me to use them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Whole Team approach to Testing in Continous Delivery</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-The-Whole-Team-Approach-to-Testing-in-Continuous-Delivery/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Whole Team approach to Testing in Continous Delivery" /><published>2018-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-The-Whole-Team-Approach-to-Testing-in-Continuous-Delivery</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-The-Whole-Team-Approach-to-Testing-in-Continuous-Delivery/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;How to test faster while pusing towards a more automated environment of continous delivery?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tutorial-day-2&quot;&gt;Tutorial Day 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;speakers&quot;&gt;Speakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a tutorial I was really looking forward to.  This session was put on by Lisa Crispin &amp;amp; Ashley Hunsberger.  I’ve read Lisa’s Agile Testing book, and I head Ashley speak at Selenium so I had a good idea of the people I was going to learn from.  So not only were the people that I knew this is a topic that is going to fit perfectly in to some changes we had upcoming here at Miami.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-the-biggest-thing-that-is-keeping-you-from-implementing-continous-delivery&quot;&gt;What is the biggest thing that is keeping you from implementing Continous Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started the session forming teams that we would work with for the rest of the day (more about my team later).  We then generated a list of things that prohibited our teams from implementing Continous Delivery.  Our team came up with several and they seemed to boil down to changing the culture.  We also talked about our teams Definition of Done (DoD) and Definition of Ready (DoR).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-continous-delivery&quot;&gt;What is Continous Delivery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continous Delivery doesn’t require full automation.  Now it is true that if it an automated solution then it is probably easier and delivery can happen quicker but that is not a requirement to implement the continous delivery ideology.  Continous delivery is really talking about the “pipeline” or flow that is taken from the code being commited in a repository to the value is actually delivered into a production environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the day Ashley and Lisa gave aus different ideas and scenarios and it was our job as a team to discuss and determine the best way for our code to be released through the pipeline.  We did determine that there is no right way.  There are many steps that you code will probable travel from check-in of code to deployment into production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really excited to get back to Miami and talk to co-workers and see what we can come up with as a solution to help our code better and easier to realease into production.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="Teams" /><category term="Continous Delivery" /><category term="CAST" /><category term="AST" /><summary type="html">How to test faster while pusing towards a more automated environment of continous delivery?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Coaching Testing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-Coaching-Testing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coaching Testing" /><published>2018-08-06T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-Coaching-Testing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/CAST2018-Coaching-Testing/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;What does it look like to be a coach of testing&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tutorial-day-1&quot;&gt;Tutorial Day 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my week of CAST 2018 with a Tutorial with Anne-Marie Charrett as she taught us about being a coach and what it looks like to coach those around us.  Specifically she was teaching about coaching testers but it was more than just that.  We spent the day talking about coaching, which is a lot like teaching but really a one-on-one experince.  We did talk a little about coaching in a group setting, but most of it was doing individual coaching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Anne-Marie started she did coaching over email and skype and slack so we tried coaching in that manner it was a little strange but that might just be because we were in the room with each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next 2 or 3 practice coaching sessions we did were in person, which felt a lot more like what I would expect to be doing at Miami.  That went a bit better than the Slack one and it was on a topic of our choice so it felt less forced and more productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also had some good conversations with attendees and made some good connections.  I would highly recommend Anne-Marie Charrett and her teaching about coaching.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="Teams" /><category term="Coaching" /><category term="CAST" /><category term="AST" /><summary type="html">What does it look like to be a coach of testing</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baking in Quality</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Baking-In-Quality/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baking in Quality" /><published>2018-06-05T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-06-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Baking-In-Quality</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Baking-In-Quality/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;How to add quality into your organization when you have a small QA Team&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="Quality" /><category term="Teams" /><summary type="html">How to add quality into your organization when you have a small QA Team</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Quest 2018</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Returning-from-QUEST-in-San-Antonio/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quest 2018" /><published>2018-05-28T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Returning-from-QUEST-in-San-Antonio</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Returning-from-QUEST-in-San-Antonio/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Returning from Quest 2018 in lovely San Antonio&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;metrics--measurements&quot;&gt;Metrics &amp;amp; Measurements&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="QAI" /><category term="QUEST" /><category term="Conferences" /><summary type="html">Returning from Quest 2018 in lovely San Antonio</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">QA or the Highway 2018</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/QAorTheHighway-2018/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="QA or the Highway 2018" /><published>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/QAorTheHighway-2018</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/QAorTheHighway-2018/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;All highways do lead to Columbus, OH&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;columbus-or-bust&quot;&gt;Columbus or Bust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another year and another good conference at OSU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;metrics--measurements&quot;&gt;Metrics &amp;amp; Measurements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have been working at Miami coming up with masurements and metrics that we can use to show that we are improving and getting better as an organization.  So I wanted to point out a few tracks that really spoke to me and ones that I will definately be bringing back to Miami to share with others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mindful-metrics&quot;&gt;Mindful Metrics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Metrics give us data. And data can give us knowledge. Knowledge is power. Therefore great metrics can give us great power. But with great power comes great responsibility. When metrics fall into the wrong hands, they can be weaponized to destroy projects and teams. But wielded responsibly, they can arm us against unstable and slow tests as well as against the tyranny of mismanagement. This talk will show how to use common metrics safely and effectively. It will also show how to extract uncommon metrics from our tests and turn this knowledge into a force for good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His Slidedeck can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slideshare.net/DmitrySharkov2/mindful-metrics-qaothw-2018-89202838&quot;&gt;slideshare&lt;/a&gt;. There were several quotes in his talk that really stuck out to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The wrong metrics are harmful.
Most Metrics are the wrong metrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just a good reminder that gathering numbers for the sake of gathering them is not always a good reason to gather them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What get’s measured, gets done, and what get’s measured, improves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When a measure becomes a target, it ceases to be a good metric.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to come up with numbers that can be used to show change and improvement, I don’t really care what the number is and I don’t want to collect numbers that can be a ‘gamed’ and become the focal point of the work instead of the work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12 RULES OF GOOD METRICS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Measure for a purpose. (Inform decisions. Measure what you want to improve.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shrink the unknown. (Recognize limitations of measures but use what you can.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seek to improve. (Avoid vanity metrics.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Delight all stakeholders. (Account for intersection and difference in needs.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Distrust all numbers. (Account for observer effect and risk compensation.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set imprecise targets. (Avoid deﬂecting from goals with tangential measures.) &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Own your metrics. (Don’t measure subordinates; measure yourself.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t connect metrics to rewards. (What is rewarded is never the organization’s true purpose.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Promote values and transparency. (Nourish self-motivation; avoid pay-for- performance.)
10.Visualize and humanize. (Don’t get caught up in numbers, forgetting people.)
11.Measure early and often.
12.Try something else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;automation&quot;&gt;Automation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we are limited in the number of QA people that we will probably ever employ at Miami, it has always been a desire of Sr. Management to Automate everything,  So I went to a few sessions about automation and what we can do to make the shift to automation easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;zapping-security-vulnerabilities-in-your-qa-process&quot;&gt;ZAPping Security Vulnerabilities in Your QA Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When your application has a security vulnerability, will you or an attacker find it first? With regression testing, new features, bug fixes, and more, finding time for security testing can be challenging. Let the free and open source OWASP Zed Attack Proxy (ZAP) help by testing for security flaws during many of the tests you already run. This session walks through using ZAP in three ways: scanning an application as you use it, writing reusable tests, and automating security scans as part of your QA process. You will learn how to attack a live application, how to target specific areas of your application for heavier scrutiny, test for specific vulnerabilities, and incorporate ZAP into your development pipeline to automate the whole process including regression testing and report generation, so that vulnerabilities are discovered the moment they are introduced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to look at running the proxy on my machine while I am doing exploratory testing on my computer and then let the software go and look for other vulnerabilities.  I’d be interested to know how different something like this is vs. the tools that our security office uses to scan the applications before they are deployed into production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;automate-your-data-free-your-mind&quot;&gt;Automate Your Data, Free Your Mind&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Data management is a crucial aspect of any project and frequent pain point for QA. Automation can be leveraged to yield multiple benefits when handling databases. These benefits include: (1) reducing time to create/maintain and remove ‘test’ data; (2) ensuring all data manipulation &amp;amp; scenarios are covered; (3) automating deployment to production and production-like environments; and (4) less manual effort invested. Automating these redundant activities help ensure testers can spend more time on valuable tasks that require human involvement. Attendees will learn each level of automation from data management to the database itself, as well as tools to enable the use of automation of CRUD (Create, Read, Update, and Delete) operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His slide deck is available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slideshare.net/qaoth/automate-your-data-free-your-mind-by-aaron-swerlein&quot;&gt;slideshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of this is about test data, and how to go about managing that test data.  This fits quite well into something that we are also working on, at Miami.  We want to reduce the copies of Personally Identifiable Information that we have on campus.  If we can work with the offices to create test data, then we should be able to accomplish this, using ideas like what he talked about in this session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;behavior-driven-developmenta-guide-to-agile-practices&quot;&gt;Behavior Driven Development—A Guide to Agile Practices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It seems as if the agile methods have lots of DD’s going on. TDD – Test Driven Development, BDD – Behavior Driven Development, and ATDD – Acceptance Test Driven Development. Adopting BDD allows for testing to be done as early as possible in the software development life cycle, promoting accurate testing, ensuring proper test coverage, and supporting the introduction of automation testing. One challenge is understanding the characteristics and benefits of “driven” approaches. Join Josh Eastman to discover ways that BDD can be employed to describe and test system behavior, user stories, and user acceptance. Josh will discuss Gherkin - the language to capture behavior descriptions and automation with cucumber and explore the four major values of BDD to ensure product quality, while driving time and cost savings. Leave this session with ideas to reduce the ambiguity and miscommunications that occur during development and testing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His slide deck is available on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slideshare.net/qaoth/behavior-driven-developmenta-guide-to-agile-practices-by-josh-eastman&quot;&gt;slideshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I work with teams to begin doing more BDD style development the info that Josh shared here will be useful as I explain what is going on.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Don Kidd</name><email>dkidd@miamioh.edu</email><uri>http://donkidd.us</uri></author><category term="QA Job" /><category term="QAOTH" /><category term="Conferences" /><summary type="html">All highways do lead to Columbus, OH</summary></entry></feed>